A new nighttime melon bread has gone on sale, and Melon bread-loving Director Murahoshi wants to try it right away.
Bon appétit!
The appearance of the melon bread is amazing, too. I hope you'll all try it too.
Night Island Idol
Melon Pan
Melon Pan.
I've loved melon bread since I was little,
I joined this group when I was in the first year of junior high school,
During self-introduction,
When I introduced myself, I sang a song saying that I was a Melon Pan-loving wonder-chan director,
I even introduced myself with the song 'I'm the Melon Pan Loving Wonder Girl Board Member',
I used to love melon bread,
Recently, you decided that you wanted to expand your hobbies.
Yes, I did.
So, on my Instagram page,
I added the hashtag 'Reju's Melon Pan Tour' to my Instagram page,
I eat melon bread from various convenience stores, supermarkets and bakeries and record them on an irregular basis.
What are you going to do?
Melon bread.
One of our members, Lori Aoi, loves Gummi Gummies every day,
We do something called Gumi-Gumi-Gumi-Gumi every day,
Melon bread has a lot of calories,
I'm a bit concerned about the calorie content of melon bread and other things,
I wish I could do it once a week,
I'm still accumulating them,
I'm still accumulating them, but I've been making the rounds.
Do you have a particular favourite melon bread shop?
At the moment, the number one shop on the list is
Melon Pan from 7-Eleven.
I've had a lot of different flavours from all of those convenience stores.
That 7-Eleven's melon bread is...
Everything is soft and fluffy.
Often melon bread is crispy on the outside, but soft on the inside.
I think that most melon breads are soft on the outside but fluffy on the inside,
But this 7-Eleven's melon bread is soft and fluffy on the outside and inside,
Moreover, it has a gentle taste,
It sounds strange to say that I want to eat gently,
When you want to relax, you should eat Seven-Eleven's fluffy melon bread.
I recommend it.
Incidentally, when I eat Melon Pan, I inevitably get tired of it halfway through,
Is there a correct way to eat melon bread in the Murakoshi-san style?
I get bored... there's not much I get bored of, but...
I drink it with tea.
With sweetness.
If you're getting a bit tired of eating sweet things...
I don't mean the bitterness of tea.
If you drink it with tea and eat it...
I think you'll be able to eat it all the way through.
I see. Tea.
Yes, with milk.
So there's a lot of tea in it.
Milk is sweet too, isn't it?
Yes, it is.
Yes.
So I think milk is good, too.
I think they go well together.
Bread and milk go well together.
Yes, they do.
I think it's a great combination.
I recommend the tea.
Oh, thank you very much.
I think, I quite recommend tea today. Straight.
When I thought I might not be able to do that for a bit.
I thought, let's make a vlog.
This programme is...
Hiromi
Maruen-san
Asa-san
Shigusa
This programme is brought to you courtesy of Mr. Daidaipanpan.
Thank you very much again today!